Welcome to my channel Winners Portfolio
I am your friend Ramesh Babu, my
channel I request only quality companies,
this stock will
create a huge bank for you in the long term. If
you visit my channel for the first time then
subscribe to my channel and
also watch my old video once, you will benefit a lot. Today
I will tell you about a number one company, I will tell you
about India's biggest multibagger stocks.
Now you can invest as much money as you want in this company, 1
lakh 10 lakh crore. You
can invest as much money as you want in this company. It is a
very good company to establish. By investing in this company,
forget about it for 10-15 years. If you
invest money in this company for your children's education and marriage, then no
one can stop you from wealth creation. The company will
double your money every year. By investing
in this company, forget about it.
Look, the name of a company is Bajaj Finance
Limited. I have followed the stock of this
company. The price of this company was ₹70,
today the price of this company is 60, if
you invest in a company then there is nothing to be afraid of.  There is
no need, in the long term you will
make crores of rupees with one company, invest for 10-15 years and
forget it,
one company will create a huge will for you. This is India's
biggest multibagger stock. If you
invest in this company, then forget for the long term
that if the market falls, then this company will also
fall. There is no need to be afraid. If you have money, then
buy more and keep investing in every fall.
You will make crores of rupees in the long term.
Ekpanishad is
a very big multibagger stock.
I am not only on YouTube, I am an
investor. If I invest in any company, I
request that company.
I invested in this company last year in 2016 at the
rate of ₹70. Today
I got a profit of Rs. 10 lakh in this company. I will
not sell this company for 10-15 years
or if there is a fall, I will give more money.
In 10-15 years, this company will make crores of
rupees. There is another company, it is a quality
company. If you invest in this company, then there is
no need to be afraid,
stop investing and study for the long term.
You will get less profit in this company.  You will get the benefit of Ponting because the
balance sheet of this company is very good,
similarly forget investing in a company having balance sheet, it will
create a huge will for you for the next 10-15 years,
look at the past performance of this company, for the
last 10 years, this company has given
9 percent CAGR returns
to the Chief Minister and from the last affair, it has given 2 percent
CAGR returns to the investor, it has given
39 percent CAGR returns for the last 13 years, it has given
162 percent returns for the last one year,
calculate the CAGR of 50%, see the medical shop
compounding,
my money in this company is one leg 70,
today how is the performance of this company, it has
given 50% return every year,
calculate once, if I look at today's
computing, then
my money in this company is one leg 70, I will not sell my money in this company for the
next 10-15 years,
how has the interest rate given by a company,
from the past performance, it has given 50 percent
CAGR returns for 10 years  Rehearsal has given 50% return,
calculate Mr. Calculate 50% rate
of interest and depression in fifteen years, Rs.
75 crore,
see this, I am Jakhm Pandey, Rs.
80 crore 75 lakh,
in sixteen years I will have earned Rs. 80 crore 75 lakh, this is
India's best multibagger
stock, invest in this company and
forget about it for the next 10-15 years, you will get a
huge will spread, if you invest in this company then there is
no need to be afraid, keep doing it
in every fall, keep buying 1122 shares,
see the venture of the match, Pandey is in the
next video